

# MARCIN WRZOŚ

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

#### **PORTFOLIO**

## PROFILE

I have experience in working on non-commercial projects with senior developers. I am a person who is characterized by a 'can-do' attitude and I am always trying to overcome the issue on my own.

I am able to write responsive pages in React with Typescript in line with the newest standards.

HOW TO REACH ME

Phone: +48 662 623 531 Email: marcin.wrzs@gmail.com

SKILLS

#### **Programming**

React, TypeScript, JavaScript, Context API, HTML, CSS (including SASS), bootstrap, webpack, github, SQL

## **Achievements:**

Radio Luz: hosting weekly radio show called Ultradzwięki Toastmasters: practicing public speaking skills Aiesec: marketing promotion of the event Dni Kariery

2017

## **EDUCATION**

#### Reskilled

Programming mentorship - work with senior developers on non commercial project in React + Typescript 2023 to present

# **Wrocław University of Economics**

Master of Finance and Accounting 2017 - 2019

#### **University of Wrocław**

Bachelor of National Security 2014 - 2017

## **PROJECTS**

## **Foodie**

Foodie is an application written in React and Typescript with custom hooks like usePagination, project uses communication via http with the external Api spoonacular. You can find the popular recipes, search for them by a category, specific name, see details of each recipe or add to favourites. Project has been published at this link by Netlify.

#### **Portfolio**

React with Typescript application which depicts my resume. Project is responsive and works on mobile devices. Functions responsible for the Day and Night mode have been moved to Context API. You are able to send me an email by contact form, which is implemented by EmailJS.

# <u>Blackjack</u>

Project is a copy of a card game called Blackjack, written in Javascript with Object Oriented Programming principles bundled in the Webpack.

WORK EXPERIENCE

## **Technical Lead, Broker Accreditation Analyst**

Axa XL | January 2023 to present

- building and Improving process areas
- coordinating process improvement initiatives

## **Analyst, Senior Financial Services Operations**

Factor Law | October 2020 to December 2022

- improving the process by VBA,
- coordinating the work allocation across the Negotiator teams

## **Security and Pricing Data Management Specialist**

Credit Suisse | January 2020 to September 2020

maintaining data of financial instruments and their prices

#### **Data & Document Specialist**

UBS | February 2019 to October 2019

• providing customer service and support to Front Office

## Junior Representative, Reconciliation

BNY Mellon | January 2018 to February 2019

- data investigation using information from different vendors
- · reconciliation against broker/custodian statements